Sajawal Fareedi

Senior Web Developer

CONTACT

+92-327-411-9581

sajawalfareedi448@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/sajawal-fareedi/

github.com/SajawalFareedi

EDUCATION

Punjab Group of Colleges

Intermediate in Computer Science

(2021-2023)

SUMMARY

Web developer with 4+ years of experience in frontend and backend development, specializing in Node.js, Next.js, and React.js. I design and build backend systems, RESTful and GraphQL APIs, microservices, and serverless solutions. With a strong track record of delivering successful projects, I am a proactive problem-solver who values best practices and clear communication.

SKILLS

- Backend Development
- Frontend Development
- Problem Solving & Critical Thinking
- Project Management & Collaboration
- Strong Communication Skills
- Unit & Integration Testing

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer | Automation

Upwork (freelance) (2021 - Present)

- Built and integrated APIs and microservices for scalable backend systems.
- Managed full-stack development, ensuring seamless frontend and backend integration.

Next.js FullStack Developer

DawahSoft PVT LTD (2024 - Present)

- Developed full-stack web apps using Next.js and Node.js.
- Enhanced performance using serverside rendering (SSR) and static site generation (SSG).

Testimonials & Client Feedback

As I've worked mostly as a freelance for the past 4 years, below are the feedbacks from my clients.

To verfiy the feedbacks, you can check out my Upwork Profile here

Client's feedback

★★★★ 5.00

"Sajawal was awesome to work with!! Very attentive and really took the time to understand what I was trying to accomplish with this project. Would hire again 10/10!"

Overall rating 5.00

Client's feedback

**** 5.00 Apr 20, 2024

"I hired this guy for a project, and he delivers what he promises. Very nice, clean coding and great understanding of the tasks given. One of my favourites on Upwork."

Overall rating 5.00

Client's feedback

★★★★ 5.00

"Outstanding performance! Sajawal made sure everything worked and even did revisions. He was always responsive to what I wanted. I recommend him for the NodeJS project you wish to take him. Looking forward to working with him again!"

Overall rating 5.00

Client's feedback

**** 5.00

"Very good coder to work with. Understands tasks very well."

**** 5.00 Mar 30, 2022

"Python or NodeJS developer? Don't look any further. I hired this guy for a few things now and he delivers what he promises. Very nice, clean coding and great understanding of the tasks given. One of my favorites on upwork."

Overall rating 5.00